saversplanet.com 2011-01-09

# Privacy Policy - SaversPlanet.com

## Privacy Policy

**Personally Identifiable Information**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

SaversPlanet.com collects no personally identifiable information unless you give it to us when ordering a screensaver or signing up for an email newsletter. No personal information given to us is used for any purpose other than what is stated - to send an email from us related to our club newsletters or to help you with your ordering information. We do not sell, rent, or give your information to any other company for any marketing purposes. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at [support@saversplanet.com.](mailto:support@saversplanet.com)

**Site Visitors**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name and IP address, but not the e-mail address (where possible). E-mail addresses are then only used by SaversPlanet.com and not sold, rented, given, or shown to any other company for any use whatsoever.

**Cookies**

Cookies are used on many download links to track referrals from this site. All full version purchases made from these downloads are then credited to SaversPlanet.com from software developer partners on a revenue sharing basis. At this time, SaversPlanet.com does not set any cookies itself.

**Ad Servers**

With respect to Ad Servers: We are currently partnering with Google to deliver ads. We cannot be responsible for the quality of ads or the operation of sites that buy ads through Google.
